[♪ somber music playing]
-[whimpering]
-[CLINE] We've had enough.
[gasps]
Well, good luck
with your next party, at least.
Then again, if I'm being honest,
I can't imagine
who'd wanna recruit a loser
who can't level up anymore
because of their awful build.
-But who knows?
-[Ruche sobbing]
[ELYMAS] They say relationships
only last
as long as the money does.
The skill point system
is particularly brutal.
[Ruche sobbing]
Didn't think
a Blood-Soaked Sword would drop.
[giggling]
[RUCHE] Seems like my skills
really helped us out
quite a bit,
don't you think?
Aw. Come on, you guys.
I thought they worked
pretty well, didn't they?
So, you think you helped us?
After visiting the dungeon
a bunch of times,
we finally got this rare drop.
So it was only a matter
of persistence and luck,
not your skills.
[ELYMAS] Could it be?
- [Ruche sobbing]
- Does she have that skill tree?
If he realized it,
then he never would've
kicked her out like that.
But based on what they said,
I'm almost positive.
She has a certain
rare skill tree
that's utterly broken
if you know how it works.
[RUCHE] I'm so sorry
for being selfish!
You don't ever
have to pay me again, okay?
I promise! Please say
you'll keep me in the party
-and I'll-- [gasps]
-[Elymas grunts]
-[panting heavily]
-[gasps]
Uh, who are you, mister?
-[ELYMAS] Hear me out!
-[screams]
-[BOTH] Huh?
-[Ruche screams]
[Elymas panting]
Please! There's nothing
to be scared of.
I just want you
to form a party with me!
A party?!
[both gasp]
[panting heavily]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
-How?
-Hmm.
[indistinct chatter]
Come on! If we form a party,
you're not gonna regret it!
So, what do you say?
Would an 80-20 split
work for you?
[gasps] Uh, I couldn't do 20%.
At that rate, it'd be almost
impossible to support myself.
I meant that you would
be getting the 80%, of course!
Is that okay?
-[RUCHE] I'd be getting more?!
-[panting]
Um, you think
you could calm down?
And I'd prefer it
if you let go of my hand too.
-Oh, please forgive me.
-[gasps]
[CLINE] What the hell's
going on here?
Mind telling me
who you think you are?
I'm Elymas.
I overheard that she's not going
to be in your party anymore.
So I wanted to come out here
and scout her for mine.
[Cline laughs]
Are you completely insane?
In combat, her performance
is so piss-poor,
she can't level properly.
That's fine with me. No problem.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[grunts, growls]
-[Ruche whimpers]
-[laughs]
Think so, huh?
Taking her off our hands
would spare us some guilt.
I just hope you don't regret
having this useless girl
-in your party.
-[gasps]
Oh, well.
Go ahead and take her then.
I wasn't asking
for your permission.
What?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[whimpering]
[grunts]
[Cline scoffs] What level
could you possibly be?
Do you have
any other party members?
I'm a Level 23
solo Heavy Knight,
and an E-rank adventurer
as well.
You're a Level 23
solo Heavy Knight?
Someone like you should be able
to tell how worthless she is,
so this makes no sense at all.
Um, excuse me.
Just so you know,
I've only made it
to Level 13 so far.
Maybe this isn't exactly
a good idea.
Like I said, not a problem.
[both gasp]
Hmm.
[growling]
-[REISS] Hey. Tell me, Cline.
-Huh?
What is it, Reiss?
[in hushed voice] Don't you
think it's a little strange
that an E-rank adventurer
would try so desperately
to recruit Ruche?
Hmm.
Maybe her skills are more useful
than we realize.
[ELYMAS]
I hope I didn't seem desperate.
Did I come on
too strong earlier?
This girl didn't do jack shit.
-Yeah, but--
-Come on, that's enough, Reiss.
Keep your mouth shut
and let her go, all right?
[Reiss sighs]
[CLINE] It's better for us
if she leaves quietly anyway.
Believe me.
Now, really think about this
for a minute.
There's no way a Heavy Knight
could have reached Level 23
all on his own.
So he's either bullshitting,
or he got kicked out
of his party.
Then again,
he could be hitting on her.
I mean,
Ruche does have a pretty face.
Well, I suppose.
[CLINE] Besides, this is going
-to work out great.
-Hmm?
We wouldn't want the rumor
to spread around that
we kicked somebody out
for their bad build.
Then it'd be hard
to get new members.
True. You have a point.
[chuckles smugly]
Hmm.
Elymas!
We've been waiting
for someone just like you.
Now, be sure
to take good care of Ruche.
[gasps]
[groans]
♪
Uh, in that case...
[panting]
I accept.
And I'm looking forward to it,
Mr. Elymas.
Yeah.
-[chuckles softly]
-So am I, Ruche.
[giggling]
[ELYMAS] I can't believe it.
I just took on
my first party member.
[CLINE] This is exciting,
isn't it?
Congrats on your new party.
You've never bought yourself
a decent weapon before,
now have you, Ruche?
[gasps]
-[Cline scoffs]
-[coins clinking]
[gasps]
Think of this 100,000 gold
as a parting gift from us.
[groans]
Hope you'll use it well.
[whimpering]
Um...
How terribly generous.
Thank you.
-[ELYMAS] No.
-[Ruche gasps]
-Don't touch those.
-Huh?
[Cline grumbles]
-[ELYMAS] Cline, was it?
-Hmm?
I want you
to pick up every single coin
-you tossed down there.
-[Cline grunts in anger]
What's the matter with you?
You honestly thought
you could throw them
all over the ground,
then say it's some kind of gift?
[seething]
[gasps]
[ELYMAS] Let's go, Ruche.
But 100,000 gold
is a lot of money.
Trust me, when it comes
to guys like him,
you never want
to owe them anything.
-[Cline grunts]
-Huh?
-Uh, right.
-Who do you think you are?
Have fun being useless together
with your defective classes!
[growling]
[grunts]
-Come on, Reiss.
-Hmm?
-Just one question first.
-[Cline gasps]
-Can I have this money?
-[gasps]
Are you kidding me?
-No, of course you can't!
These coins are mine.
You got that?!
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, hey.
[WAITRESS] Be right there.
Please be patient.
[chuckles] Thank you so much
for inviting me
to join your party!
I really appreciate it,
Mr. Elymas!
Though, I still can't help
feeling a little worried
about this too,
because I just don't think
I'm powerful enough.
[ELYMAS]
You don't have to worry.
If we kill monsters
suited to your skill trees,
-you'll level up.
-Actually...
-Hmm?
-...you've been so kind to me,
I wanted to ask, Mr. Elymas.
Is the reason
you've been so helpful
because you fell in love
at first sight?
-[giggling]
-I beg your pardon?
This whole time,
I've been wondering why somebody
who's way above my level
would ever
wanna stand up for me.
And that's all
I could come up with.
Uh, but to be fair,
I can be downright adorable.
And I, um,
I think
you're very attractive too.
So please don't get me wrong.
But maybe it'd be better
if we just start out
as friends, okay?
-[giggling]
-[grunting frustratedly]
Although, I'm really flattered,
you should know
I'm not that easy. Tee-hee!
-Ruche.
-Huh?
The Lady Luck skill tree.
You have it, don't you?
Huh?
What?
[indistinct chatter]
-Ruche.
-Huh?
The Lady Luck skill tree.
You have it, don't you?
Huh?
What?
[birds chirping]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Ruche sighs]
[ELYMAS] In Magic World,
dungeons are the nightmares
of the sleeping God of Creation,
whose name is Alxeros.
Over the span of an eternity,
he created infinite gods
and worlds from nothing.
But Alxeros, who reigned
as the everlasting supreme god
and existed since the beginning
of time itself,
lost his mind
and was sealed away
by the very gods he created.
However,
his most frightening nightmares
are beginning
to affect our reality.
They're creating gates
in the real world,
which are producing aberrant,
blood-thirsty monsters
and malevolent demons.
[gasps]
-There it is.
-[gasps]
Those are dungeons,
also referred to as Dreamholes.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Angel's Playbox Entrance.
Recommended level, 50.
Are you positive you want me
to go through with this,
Mr. Elymas?
I mean, take a look at
what I have to offer.
Do you see those stats?
You should really
keep this private
and not show other people.
Are you being serious?!
It's all right. I'm not worried.
You seem pretty trustworthy,
so I don't think
you'll tell anybody.
Besides, it'd be better for you
to abandon me right now
than to start
getting your hopes up
only for me to disappoint you.
I only have one attack skill
called Dice Thrust.
And I can't even use that
unless I get lucky
and roll a six.
If I'd taken
The Fool's Acrobatics
or put points
into Attack Booster,
I wouldn't even be in this mess.
[laughing awkwardly]
Well, I really screwed up,
didn't I?
It's all right.
[gasps]
[cape rustling]
Truth is, I need you
more than you know.
Huh? Uh, what does that mean?
Um, I don't know too much
about that sort of thing.
So you'll just have to be
a little more direct with me,
or I won't understand
what you're saying.
Uh, but I-- I suppose it's wrong
of me to say that.
It's not fair
to either of us, is it?
I am so sorry.
Oh, of course.
Now the two of us
are going to grind out
an easy 30 million gold
and get you up to Level 30
before we leave here.
What?! So how the heck
are we supposed to do that?!
-Let's go.
-All right.
[whooshing]
[cape rustling]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[ELYMAS]
The recommended level is 50,
but I'm familiar
with all the monsters
-that spawn here.
-[gasps]
We won't encounter
any serious danger.
We're only going to stick
to the upper floors
and grind levels for a while.
I'll lure the enemies
over to me,
then you can start
attacking them.
Time to use
that Ironpiercer knife.
I was nervous, but I still made
the decision to come this far.
You even bought
this expensive knife
for me to use out here.
So there's no way
I'm gonna start wimping out now!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Ironpiercer. Attack plus three.
Market price, 550,000 gold.
This knife is effective
against tough opponents.
When damage is applied,
reduce the target's defense
by 15%
before calculating damage.
Don't worry, 'cause you can
count on me, Mr. Elymas!
I'll do what I can to live up
to your inexplicable confidence
and expectations!
[grunting]
Oh, good. Glad you're finally
feeling confident.
[RUCHE] To show my gratitude
for this knife,
I'll do everything I can
to protect you!
[Elymas laughs]
My job's to protect you.
-[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear!
-[Ruche gasps]
[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear!
[gasps]
[PATCHWORK BEAR]
Bear! Bear! Bear!
Bear!
[ELYMAS] There it is.
A Patchwork Bear.
It may look fluffy and adorable,
but there is nothing cute
about its level.
[ELYMAS] It has an attack of 22.
So even if you manage
to get hit,
-you'll still survive.
-[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear!
There's no way you'd be able
to resist
a crit from that thing,
but I can
shut it down completely
by throwing the bear off balance
-right as it's about to attack.
-[Ruche gasps]
I don't get it. How do you
already know all that?
-Huh?
-Be honest.
-Do you like Patchwork Bears?
-[laughs awkwardly]
[ELYMAS] No,
I can't say that I do.
[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear! Bear!
[ELYMAS]
I'll take care of its attacks.
Then you can strike
from its blind spots
-and take it down.
-Uh, right!
Watch out
for those claws and fangs.
-Heard.
-'Kay.
[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear!
Shadow Stomp!
[ELYMAS] I bought this skill
with points
from the Mad Headder fight,
and now I can use it
to help Ruche level up.
-[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear! Bear!
-[grunts]
My shadows can stretch
pretty far. Be careful.
Uh. Yeah, I got it.
Mm. Wait. You told me
I needed to watch out
for its claws and fangs,
but I'm not seeing even one.
Are you sure you were thinking
about the right monster?
[Patchwork Bear growls]
Huh?
[Patchwork Bear grunting]
[gasps]
[Patchwork Bear roaring]
-[Elymas grunting]
-[sword slashes]
[gasps]
[sighs] Glad I have this shield.
Trying to survive attacks
while staying
in the same spot is a pain.
[Patchwork Bear grunts]
'Kay. Your turn.
-Attack till it's destroyed.
-Uh. Right!
[pants]
-[Patchwork Bear groans]
-[gasps]
Well, this should be
a little easier.
It doesn't even look cute now!
[yells]
-[grunting]
-[Patchwork Bear groaning]
[grunts, yells]
-[grunts]
-[Patchwork Bear groans]
[Ruche gasps]
That took more attacks
than I expected.
But we still brought it down.
[sighs]
Ruche, so how many levels
did you gain from--
-What?
-[gasps]
Come on, Mr. Patchwork Bear!
You can't do this!
Please drop something!
Don't leave me hanging here!
[sobbing] This is so awful!
I'm going to be kicked out
of my party again.
I just know it!
-[crying]
-[ELYMAS] Hey.
Don't worry, all right?
We only killed it
for the EXP, anyway.
I plan to kill a few more,
so I'm sure something
will drop eventually.
-[distant thudding]
-Hmm?
-Huh?
-[PATCHWORK BEAR] Bear!
[ELYMAS] Would you look at that?
Speak of the devil.
Okay, same plan as before.
Let's go.
Right!
-[Elymas, Ruche grunting]
-[swords slashing]
[grunts]
-[Patchwork Bear groans]
-[yells]
[Patchwork Bear groans]
-[Patchwork Bear groans]
-[grunts]
[crashes]
[Ruche squeals delightedly]
[laughs]
Look at this!
It was definitely
worth the wait!
We finally got something!
They both dropped items!
That's two in a row for us.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Bear Shield. Defense plus 12.
Market price, 200,000 gold.
A cute round Bear Shield.
[RUCHE] I bet you're glad
you brought me
out here now, right?
-Will these things be useful?
-Huh?
-Oh. Um, sure.
-[giggling]
We might as well
take them with us.
Okay. That sounds
like a great idea.
-[ELYMAS] That's so strange.
-[giggling]
These items don't usually drop
one after another.
Did I misremember
the drop rate out here?
-[giggling]
- Wait, that's right.
[ELYMAS] Ruche's Cat's Paw skill
is a special skill
that increases
a player's luck by 500%.
If she started out
with a luck stat
that was fairly high
to begin with,
then I suppose
all of this makes sense.
[Ruche giggling]
Didn't think
a Blood-Soaked Sword would drop.
[Ruche giggles]
Seems like my skills
really helped us out
quite a bit,
don't you think?
So it was only a matter
of persistence and luck,
not your skills.
[ELYMAS] But why didn't
Cline's party realize how much
she was actually improving
their drop rate?
After such a weak performance
-like that--
-[ELYMAS] Oh, right.
They couldn't see her value
because they're a newbie party.
In this world, there isn't a lot
of information on monsters.
They must have gotten used to
high drop rates
from the very beginning.
[giggles]
How was that?
Am I being useful, Mr. Elymas?
Yeah. Thank you.
I'm really grateful that
you decided to team up with me.
[squeals excitedly]
[giggles]
Guess you wanted
to get your hands
on these little Bear Shields
pretty badly, didn't you?
Should we collect
10 more of them?
[ELYMAS] No.
You've gained enough levels.
The real work starts right now.
Mm. Huh?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 20 has been reached.
[RUCHE] Oh, wow! You're right!
When did that happen?
-[giggles]
-[ELYMAS] At this point,
the new goal for us
is hunting Golden Raana.
[gasps]
[RUCHE] Uh, Golden Raana?!
[croaks]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] So far, Ruche's power
is even more impressive
than I thought it'd be.
But I know it's only
a small fraction
of what she can do.
No, I'm not referring
to those two Bear Shields.
I'm not equipping them.
In any case,
the two of us can finally
focus on what we came
to this dungeon for.
With everything else
out of the way,
the real work starts right now.
Next time,
"Golden Raana Farming."
Every game should have
at least one bonus character!